Helaongjiang Province is a northern Chinese city bordering Russia.
It has a population of 1 million, once one of China's largest coal cities.
Hugon helped propel the nation's strong economic growth.
Dwindling demand for coal following an economic downturn has cast a shadow over the industry.
This once flourishing city now seeds with anger and frustration.
In this episode, we examine the plight of struggling workers in a city with an uncertain future.
Leijing is 11 kilometers from Central Kugan.
It was completed last year as part of the government's redevelopment plan.
The 30 buildings contain 1,600 homes.
A small store stands on a corner.
It sells food, alcohol, and daily necessities.
The owner, Wang DeFu, opened this store when he moved into the complex.
He runs the shop with his wife, Jiang Nana.
Most customers are residents of the complex.
Wong is a former coal miner.
Like many families here, he started mining with his father.
He got his first job in the mines at 16.
But after the recession seven years ago, his income plummeted.
Last year, he finally quit mining.
The economy is good.
There are no more than 100 people in China.
The economy is getting more and more popular.
The cars are getting more and more popular.
Now you have to be more popular.
Cool Fields were discovered in Hugan in 1914.
Since then, more than 100 coal mines have been developed.
Mosting some of the highest output in China,
Kugans coal mines supported China's high economic growth.
Starting around the turn of the century, the city enjoyed double digit GDP growth for
more than ten years.
In the 2010s, however, the economy hit a slum.
Man for coal plunged as funding shifted from coal-based heavy industries to high-tech,
eco-friendly ones.
Many coal mines are now suspended,
only lives with his parents,
wife and young daughter.
It's hard for him to work out of town
while raising a child.
Long's mother, Leo Yifeng, helped fund the opening of the store after her son quit working in the mines.
Meng's family is wary of shoplifters, an alarming trend in the complex.
I'm going to the next house.
The three of us are a housekeeper.
How to say it?
The one with the head is not going to be there.
Don't move that thing.
I'm going to put the key.
You have to move a little bit.
You can buy it on the house.
You can see it in the house.
You can put it behind.
I'm going to put it on the housekeeper.
This is a serious threat for a small store that barely makes a profit.
makes a profit. The district is full of brand new buildings, but in the streets and
and pauses, men shat, and walk around aimlessly.
Most of the residents are coal miners.
I have been in the country for a while.
Who are you?
I have been working for a few years.
A few years.
What do you do?
You collect it and there are people who are still working.
Can you not come?
No, I can't.
You are now on the 6th and 8th floor.
I am on the 6th floor.
When we were in the city, we had to open the door.
We had to open the door and we had to open the door.
We had to open the door.
If there were any other places,
we would have to stop immediately.
Those with similar complaints gather together.
Gather together.
Suddenly angry shout echoed through the streets.
Angry Shouts echoed through the streets.
I don't want to eat today.
It's a little too cold.
It's cold.
Nana, Nana, Nana, Nana, Nana.
The couples fighting in the streets, a drunk in broad daylight.
The frustration of the residents only worsens.
Hong notices a sales trend.
Despite week overall sales, alcohol is selling strong.
Hong's family owns five hundred.
Hong's family owns five homes in this complex, which is actually a serious problem.
The complex was redeveloped on farmland the government acquired, and many former residents
received condos in return. Hong used one of those condos to open shop. He has been renting
this extra residence to earn sight in come. But the tenant recently moved out.
Hogan has the lowest real estate prices among cities of its size. People joke that land
prices are as cheap as cabbage.
Real estate ads are everywhere.
Real estate agencies have shut down or been forced
to switch industries.
One's family used to earn $300 in rent a year.
They haven't found any new tenants.
There are people who are willing to go to the market.
Do you think the market is cheap?
Now it's not cheap.
You two are going to be cheap.
The red is not good for health.
It's too small.
It's not good for health.
Desperate to find a tenant,
you made a small ad.
With winners soon approaching Hogan,
landlords will have to pay for the central heating
of all homes, even empty ones.
Unless they find tenants soon,
the orange will be in the red.
The more condos they own,
the more dire the need for tenants.
Shuai Baohu runs a cram school for local youth.
Born in Hukang, Shuai has lived here his entire life.
Mm.
Yeah.
This vacant lot was once full of stores.
Shoé's Crem School offers courses to help students prepare for the public servant
exam.
Local youths increasingly aim to become public servants.
Shoé has helped more than 100 students pass the public servant exam since opening the
school three years ago.
I've been doing a lot of things, but I don't know how to handle it.
And the next thing I do is to handle it.
How do you explain this?
I started to think about it.
I've been thinking about how to explain it to my own business.
I've been working on it for a long time.
I've been working on my own business.
I have to learn more from Lin Dao.
I have to learn more from Shibu.
If you can't, I'm really good.
If you can't, I can't.
You have to learn from me.
In fact, we have some other reasons.
We can't just explain.
I'm wrong.
I can't just say.
What do you want to say?
It's my fault.
I'm not a professional.
It's my job.
I'm not good.
I have to learn from you.
What do we do in the end?
Becoming a public servant is the one hope left for young people here.
Many companies in Hong Kong are stayed on and have deep rooted social
Socialist ideals. That's why people prefer a stable job, rather than their own businesses.
with the surging number of candidates aiming to become public servants.
Crem School competition is heating up.
Getting students is getting harder.
Today, Shuiway distributes flyers all over town.
I don't know.
But I know it.
How much is the monthly salary?
The monthly salary is 4,000.
Then...
Is it worth it?
Who is it?
How much is the monthly salary?
A little tired.
Do you have a long way to go?
Of course.
I can be better if I can't use it.
This is a small greener's home,
less than a year before.
That's a big change.
I have to help you.
If there's a problem,
you can't work on a small house.
You know,
we are married.
We were in the wild at the time.
But I didn't get to ask,
how many acres are there?
I've had to study hard.
And now I can't find a job.
I'm learning to live in the countryside.
I have to make some clothes.
This is a good idea.
I'm looking for a job at a country.
I have to clean the market.
I haven't done a job,
I need a job,
I'm setting people up for work,
but keep a good distance from the country.
He's a big job.
People can't find a job that they want whatever they want.
If the economy is up to the country,
they won't be able to afford it.
He's a big job.
Now, you're talking.
Very good.
But the economy is up to you,
The legion complex, many men stand around and chat.
Even the elderly are worried about the city's future.
The decline of coal mines is negatively affecting the retired population, and exposing many once-hidden problems.
How long have you been in the countryside?
I have been asking you about the small house, how long have you been in the countryside?
The small house is not small, you don't have to be a little.
How do you know?
The small house is not a small.
It's not a little.
You don't have to be a little.
I am a little better now.
What's up?
I am very angry but I can't catch it.
I want to kill all of you.
There wasn't much time left for me.
I have any time left.
Are we recording?
No, I'm doing the same thing.
She believes that to save Hudaon, young people must be encouraged to stay here, but he's not particularly optimistic.
Local's who have seen who gone flourish and decline are now feeling frustrated and angry.
The government has acknowledged 69 resource dependent cities.
that now suffer from drastically shrinking industries.